{
  "isTheory": true,
  "openingRemarks": "Find the solution to the following equations",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(17x+ 12 = 54 - 4x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n17x+12&=54-4x\\\\\n17x+4x&=54-12\\\\\n21x&=42\\\\\n\\dfrac{21x}{21}&=\\dfrac{42}{21}\\\\\nx&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 17x+12 \\) if \\( x=2 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=17(2)+12\\\\\n&=34+12\\\\\n&=46\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 54-4x \\) if \\( x=2 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=54-4(2) \\\\\n&=54-8 \\\\\n&=46\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 6",
        " 2",
        " \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
        " 46"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6x - 16 = 5x - 9 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6x-16&=5x-9\\\\\n6x-5x&=-9+16\\\\\nx&=7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 6x-16 \\) if \\( x=7 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=6(7)-16\\\\\n&=42-16\\\\\n&=26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 5x-9 \\) if \\( x=7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5(7)-9 \\\\\n&=35-9 \\\\\n&=26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 26",
        " 10",
        " 33",
        " 7"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4x - 4 = 3x + 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x-4&=3x+2\\\\\n4x-3x&=2+4\\\\\nx&=6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 4x-4 \\) if \\( x=6 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(6)-4\\\\\n&=24-4\\\\\n&=20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3x+2 \\) if \\( x=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(6)+2 \\\\\n&=18+2 \\\\\n&=20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 6",
        " 26",
        " 20",
        " 14"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(13x - 25 = 9x - 13 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n13x-25&=9x-13\\\\\n13x-9x&=-13+25\\\\\n4x&=12\\\\\n\\dfrac{4x}{4}&=\\dfrac{12}{4}\\\\\nx&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 13x-25 \\) if \\( x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=13(3)-25\\\\\n&=39-25\\\\\n&=14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 9x-13 \\) if \\( x=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=9(3)-13 \\\\\n&=27-13 \\\\\n&=14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 14",
        " 25",
        " 3",
        " 17"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9x + 2 = 7x + 15 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9x+2&=7x+15\\\\\n9x-7x&=15-2\\\\\n2x&=13\\\\\n\\dfrac{2x}{2}&=\\dfrac{13}{2}\\\\\nx&=6.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  9x+2\\) if \\( x=6.5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=9(6.5)+2\\\\\n&=58.5+2\\\\\n&=60.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 7x+15 \\) if \\( x=6.5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=7(6.5)+15\\\\\n&=45.5+15\\\\\n&=60.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 6.5",
        " 60.5",
        " 67",
        " 5.6"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3x + 39 = 2x + 42 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x+39&=2x+42\\\\\n3x-2x&=42-39\\\\\nx&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  3x+39\\) if \\( x= 3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(3)+39\\\\\n&=9+39\\\\\n&=48\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  2x+42\\) if \\( x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(3)+42\\\\\n&=6+42\\\\\n&=48\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 3",
        " 40",
        " 48",
        " 51"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5x - 3x = 36 - x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5x-3x&=36-x\\\\\n5x-3x+x&=36\\\\\n3x&=36\\\\\n\\dfrac{3x}{3} &= \\dfrac{36}{3}\\\\\nx&=12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  5x-3x\\) if \\( x=12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5(12)-3(12)\\\\\n&=60-36\\\\\n&=24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 36-x \\) if \\( x= 12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=36-12\\\\\n&=24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 24",
        " 36",
        " 13",
        " 12"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7x - 12 + 5 = 8x - 24 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7x-12+5&=8x-24\\\\\n7x-8x&=-24+12-5\\\\\n-x&=-17\\\\\nx&=17\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7x-12+5  \\) if \\( x= 17\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=7(17)-12+5\\\\\n&=119-7\\\\\n&=112\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  8x-24\\) if \\( x= 17\\)</div>\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=8(17)-24\\\\\n&=136-24\\\\\n&=112\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 112",
        " 17",
        " -17",
        " -112"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(30 - x + 12 = 3x + 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n30-x+12&=3x+2\\\\\n30+12-2&=3x+x\\\\\n40&=4x\\\\\n\\dfrac{40}{4}&=\\dfrac{4x}{4}\\\\\n10&=x\\\\\nx&=10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  30-x+12\\) if \\( x= 10\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=30-10+12\\\\\n&=32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3x+2 \\) if \\( x= 10\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(10)+2\\\\\n&=30+2\\\\\n&=32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -32",
        " -10",
        " 42",
        " 10"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6x - 30 = 60 - 8x - 20 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6x-30&=60-8x-20\\\\\n6x+8x&=60-20+30\\\\\n14x&=70\\\\\n\\dfrac{14x}{14}&=\\dfrac{70}{14}\\\\\nx&=5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 6x-30 \\) if \\( x=5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=6(5)-30\\\\\n&=30-30\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 60-8x-20 \\) if \\( x= 5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=60-8(5)-20\\\\\n&=60-40-20\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 5",
        " -5",
        " 0",
        " 14"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9x - 16 = 3x - (x - 5) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9x-16&=3x-(x-5)\\\\\n9x-16&=3x-x+5\\\\\n9x-3x+x&=5+16\\\\\n7x&=21\\\\\n\\dfrac{7x}{7}&=\\dfrac{21}{7}\\\\\nx&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 9x-16 \\) if \\( x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=9(3)-16\\\\\n&=27-16\\\\\n&=11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3x-(x-5) \\) if \\( x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(3)-(3-5)\\\\\n&=9--2\\\\\n&=11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 11",
        " 21",
        " 7",
        " 3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5x - 10 + 2x = 6(x + 1) - x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5x-10+2x&=6(x+1)-x\\\\\n5x-10+2x&=6x+6-x\\\\\n5x+2x-6x+x&=6+10\\\\\n2x&=16\\\\\n\\dfrac{2x}{2}&=\\dfrac{16}{2}\\\\\nx&=8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5x-10+2x  \\) if \\( x=8 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5(8)-10+2(8)\\\\\n&=40-10+16\\\\\n&=46\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 6(x+1)-x \\) if \\( x=8 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=6(8+1)-8\\\\\n&=6(9) - 8\\\\\n&=54-8\\\\\n&=46\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 46",
        " 54",
        " 8",
        " 38"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(5x + 1) = x + 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(5x+1)&=x+2\\\\\n10x+2&=x+2\\\\\n10x-x&=2-2\\\\\n9x&=0\\\\\n\\dfrac{9x}{9} &= \\dfrac{0}{9}\\\\\nx&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  2(5x+1)\\) if \\( x=0 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(5(0)+1)\\\\\n&=2(0+1)\\\\\n&=2(1)\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( x+2 \\) if \\( x=0 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=0+2\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 2",
        " 0",
        " 1",
        " -2"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5(x + 1) = 2(x - 5) + 6 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5(x+1)&=2(x-5)+6\\\\\n5x+5&=2x-10+6\\\\\n5x-2x&=-10+6-5\\\\\n3x&=-9\\\\\n\\dfrac{3x}{3} &= \\dfrac{-9}{3}\\\\\nx&=-3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  5(x+1)\\) if \\( x= -3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5(-3+1)\\\\\n&=5(-2)\\\\\n&=-10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2(x-5)+6 \\) if \\( x= -3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(-3-5)+6\\\\\n&=2(-8)+6\\\\\n&=-16+6\\\\\n&=-10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -10",
        " 10",
        " 3",
        " -3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3(x - 2) - 2(x - 3) - 5 = 0 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3(x-2)-2(x-3)-5&=0\\\\\n3x-6-2x+6-5&=0\\\\\n3x-2x&=6-6+5\\\\\nx&=5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  3(x-2)-2(x-3)-5\\) if \\( x=5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(5-2)-2(5-3)-5\\\\\n&=3(3)-2(2)-5\\\\\n&=9-4-5\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 0",
        " 5",
        " -5",
        " 6"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\((3 - 2x) + 3(1 - 4x) - 4(1 - 5x) = 2(1 - 3x) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n(3-2x)+3(1-4x)-4(1-5x)&=2(1-3x)\\\\\n3-2x+3-12x-4+20x&=2-6x\\\\\n-2x-12x+20x+6x&=2+4-3-3\\\\\n12x&=0\\\\\n\\dfrac{12x}{12} &= \\dfrac{0}{12}\\\\\nx&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  (3-2x)+3(1-4x)-4(1-5x)\\) if \\( x=0 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=(3-2(0))+3(1-4(0))-4(1-5(0))\\\\\n&=(3-0)+3(1-0)-4(1-0)\\\\\n&=3+3(1)-4(1)\\\\\n&=3+3-4\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  2(1-3x)\\) if \\( x= 0\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(1-3(0))\\\\\n&=2(1-0)\\\\\n&=2(1)\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 0",
        " 2",
        " 12",
        " -2"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3x - \\dfrac{1}{3} = 44\\frac{2}{3} - 2x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x-\\dfrac{1}{3} &= 44\\tfrac{2}{3} - 2x\\\\\n3x-\\dfrac{1}{3}&=\\dfrac{134}{3}-2x\\\\\n3 \\times \\left(3x-\\dfrac{1}{3}\\right)&= 3 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{134}{3}-2x\\right)\\\\\n3 \\times 3x - 3 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3} &= 3 \\times \\dfrac{134}{3} - 3 \\times 2x\\\\\n9x-1&=134-6x\\\\\n9x+6x&=134+1\\\\\n15x&=135\\\\\n\\dfrac{15x}{15} &= \\dfrac{135}{15}\\\\\nx&=9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3x-\\dfrac{1}{3} \\) if \\( x= 15\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(9)-\\dfrac{1}{3}\\\\\n&=27-\\dfrac{1}{3}\\\\\n&=26.\\overline{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  44\\tfrac{2}{3}-2x\\) if \\( x=9 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{134}{3}-2(9)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{134}{3}-18\\\\\n&=26.\\overline{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " \\(26\\frac{2}{3}\\)",
        " 26",
        " 9",
        " -9"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2x - 3 = \\dfrac{1}{5} - 6x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2x-3&=\\dfrac{1}{5}-6x\\\\\n5 \\times (2x-3) &= 5 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{1}{5}-6x\\right)\\\\\n5(2x-3) &= 5 \\times \\dfrac{1}{5} - 5 \\times 6x\\\\\n10x-15&=1-30x\\\\\n10x+30x&=1+15\\\\\n40x&=16\\\\\n\\dfrac{40x}{40}&=\\dfrac{16}{40}\\\\\nx&=0.4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2x-3 \\) if \\( x=0.4 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(0.4)-3\\\\\n&=0.8-3\\\\\n&=-2.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{1}{5}-6x \\) if \\( x=0.4 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1}{5} - 6(0.4)\\\\\n&=0.2-2.4\\\\\n&=-2.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 0.4",
        " -2",
        " -2.2",
        " -3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5x + 3 = \\dfrac{29}{3} - \\dfrac{15}{9}x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5x+3&=\\dfrac{29}{3} - \\dfrac{15x}{9}\\\\\n9 \\times \\left(5x+3\\right) &=9 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{29}{3} - \\dfrac{15x}{9}\\right)\\\\\n9(5x+3) &= 9 \\times \\dfrac{29}{3} - 9 \\times \\dfrac{15x}{9}\\\\\n45x+27&=87-15x\\\\\n45+15x&=87-27\\\\\n60x&=60\\\\\n\\dfrac{60x}{60} &= \\dfrac{60}{60}\\\\\nx&=1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 5x+3 \\) if \\( x=1 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5(1)+3\\\\\n&=5+3\\\\\n&=8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  \\dfrac{29}{3} - \\dfrac{15x}{9}\\) if \\( x=1 \\)</div>\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{29}{3} - \\dfrac{15(1)}{9}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{29}{3} - \\dfrac{15}{9}\\\\\n&=8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 8",
        " 60",
        " 9",
        " 1"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(30x - 3\\frac{1}{2} = 3\\frac{1}{2} + 2x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n30x-3\\tfrac{1}{2} &= 3\\tfrac{1}{2} + 2x\\\\\n30x-\\dfrac{7}{2} &= \\dfrac{7}{2} + 2x\\\\\n2 \\times \\left(30x-\\dfrac{7}{2}\\right) &= 2 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{7}{2} + 2x\\right)\\\\\n2 \\times 30x - 2 \\times \\dfrac{7}{2} &= 2 \\times \\dfrac{7}{2} + 2 \\times 2x\\\\\n60x-7&=7+4x\\\\\n60x-4x&=7+7\\\\\n56x&=14\\\\\n\\dfrac{56x}{56} &= \\dfrac{14}{56}\\\\\nx&=0.25\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 30x-3\\tfrac{1}{2} \\) if \\( x= 0.25\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=30(0.25)-\\dfrac{7}{2}\\\\\n&=7.5-3.5\\\\\n&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  3\\tfrac{1}{2} + 2x\\) if \\( x=0.25 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{7}{2}+2(0.25)\\\\\n&=3.5+0.5\\\\\n&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " \\(\\dfrac{7}{2}\\)",
        " 4",
        " 0",
        " 0.25"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3x - \\dfrac{x}{3} = 42 - 2x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x - \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 42-2x\\\\\n3 \\times \\left(3x - \\dfrac{x}{3}\\right) &= 3 \\times (42-2x)\\\\\n3 \\times 3x - 3 \\times \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 3(42-2x)\\\\\n9x-x&=126-6x\\\\\n9x-x+6x&=126\\\\\n14x&=126\\\\\n\\dfrac{14x}{14} &= \\dfrac{126}{14}\\\\\nx&=9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  3x - \\dfrac{x}{3} \\) if \\( x= 9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(9) - \\dfrac{9}{3}\\\\\n&=27-3\\\\\n&=24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 42-2x \\) if \\( x= 9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=42-2(9)\\\\\n&=42-18\\\\\n&=24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 9",
        " 3",
        " 24",
        " 33"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3x + \\dfrac{5}{4}x = 34 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x+\\dfrac{5}{4}x &= 34\\\\\n4 \\times (3x+\\dfrac{5}{4}x) &= 4 \\times 34\\\\\n4 \\times 3x + 4 \\times \\dfrac{5}{4}x &= 136\\\\\n12x + 5x &= 136\\\\\n17x &= 136 \\\\\n\\dfrac{17x}{17} &= \\dfrac{136}{17}\\\\\nx&=8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = 34 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3x+\\dfrac{5}{4}x \\) if \\( x= 8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(8)+\\dfrac{5}{4}(8) \\\\\n&=24+10\\\\\n&=34\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 42",
        " 8",
        " 34",
        " 26"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(x - \\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x}{3} = 5 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx - \\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 5\\\\\n6 \\times \\left(x - \\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x}{3}\\right) &= 6 \\times 5\\\\\n6 \\times x - 6 \\times \\dfrac{x}{2} + 6 \\times \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 30\\\\\n6x - 3x + 2x &= 30\\\\\n5x &= 30\\\\\n\\dfrac{5x}{5} &= \\dfrac{30}{5}\\\\\nx&=6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = 5 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( x - \\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x}{3} \\) if \\( x= 6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=6 - \\dfrac{6}{2} + \\dfrac{6}{3}\\\\\n&=6-3+2\\\\\n&=5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 5",
        " \\(\\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
        " 6",
        " -6"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} = \\dfrac{x}{4} - 1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} &= \\dfrac{x}{4} - 1\\\\\n12 \\times \\left( \\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3}\\right) &= 12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x}{4} - 1\\right)\\\\\n12\\left(\\dfrac{x}{2}\\right) - 12\\left(\\dfrac{x}{3}\\right) &= 12\\left(\\dfrac{x}{4}\\right) - 12(1)\\\\\n6x-4x&=3x-12\\\\\n6x-4x-3x&=-12\\\\\n-x&=-12\\\\\nx&=12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3}  \\) if \\( x= 12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{12}{2} - \\dfrac{12}{3}\\\\\n&=6-4\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  \\dfrac{x}{4} - 1\\) if \\( x=12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{12}{4} - 1\\\\\n&=3-1\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 2",
        " 6",
        " 14",
        " 12"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{4}x = 19 - x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{4}x &= 19 - x \\\\\n12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{4}x\\right) &= 12 \\times (19 - x) \\\\\n12\\left(\\dfrac{1}{3}x\\right) + 12\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}x\\right) &= 12(19-x)\\\\\n4x + 3x &= 228 - 12x \\\\\n7x + 12x &= 228\\\\\n19x &= 228 \\\\\n\\dfrac{19x}{19} &= \\dfrac{228}{19}\\\\\nx&=12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{4}x \\) if \\( x= 12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1}{3}(12) + \\dfrac{1}{4}(12)\\\\\n&=4+3\\\\\n&=7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  19 - x\\) if \\( x= 12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=19 - 12\\\\\n&=7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -12",
        " 12",
        " 21",
        " 7"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} = \\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{x}{5} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} &= \\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{x}{5}\\\\\n60 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3}\\right) &= 60 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{x}{5}\\right)\\\\\n60\\left(\\dfrac{x}{2}\\right) - 60\\left(\\dfrac{x}{3}\\right) &= 60\\left(\\dfrac{x}{4}\\right) - 60\\left(\\dfrac{x}{5}\\right)\\\\\n30x - 20x &= 15x - 12x \\\\\n30x - 20x - 15x + 12x &= 0\\\\\n7x &= 0\\\\\n\\dfrac{7x}{7} &= \\dfrac{0}{7} \\\\\nx&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} \\) if \\( x= 0\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{0}{2} - \\dfrac{0}{3}\\\\\n&=0-0\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  \\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{x}{5}\\) if \\( x= 0\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{0}{4} - \\dfrac{0}{5}\\\\\n&=0-0\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 5",
        " 10",
        " 6",
        " 0"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(x + \\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} = 17 - \\dfrac{x}{4} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx + \\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 17 - \\dfrac{x}{4}\\\\\n12 \\times \\left(x + \\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} \\right)&= 12 \\times \\left(17 - \\dfrac{x}{4}\\right)\\\\\n12 \\times x + 12 \\times \\dfrac{x}{2} - 12 \\times \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 12 \\times 17 - 12 \\times \\dfrac{x}{4}\\\\\n12x+6x-4x&=204-3x\\\\\n12x+6x-4x+3x&=204\\\\\n\\dfrac{17x}{17} &= \\dfrac{204}{17}\\\\\nx&=12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( x + \\dfrac{x}{2} - \\dfrac{x}{3} \\) if \\( x= 12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=12 + \\dfrac{12}{2} - \\dfrac{12}{3}\\\\\n&=12 + 6 - 4\\\\\n&=14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  17 - \\dfrac{x}{4}\\) if \\( x=12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=17 - \\dfrac{12}{4}\\\\\n&=17-3\\\\\n&=14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 12",
        " 26",
        " 14",
        " 32"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(15x - 9 = 20 + \\dfrac{x + 1}{3} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n15x - 9 &= 20 + \\dfrac{x+1}{3}\\\\\n3 \\times (15x-9) &= 3 \\times \\left(20 + \\dfrac{x+1}{3}\\right)\\\\\n3 \\times 15x - 3 \\times 9 &= 3 \\times 20 + 3 \\times \\dfrac{x+1}{3}\\\\\n45x-27 &= 60 + (x+ 1)\\\\\n45x-27 &= 60 + x+ 1\\\\\n45x-x&=60+1+27\\\\\n44x&=88\\\\\n\\dfrac{44x}{44} &= \\dfrac{88}{44}\\\\\nx&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  15x - 9\\) if \\( x=2 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=15(2)-9\\\\\n&=30-9\\\\\n&=21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 20 + \\dfrac{x+1}{3} \\) if \\( x=2 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=20 + \\dfrac{2+1}{3}\\\\\n&=20 + \\dfrac{3}{3}\\\\\n&= 20 + 1\\\\\n&= 21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 21",
        " 23",
        " 2",
        " 19"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x+1}{3} = 14 + \\dfrac{6 - x}{4} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x+1}{3} &= 14 + \\dfrac{6-x}{4}\\\\\n12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x+1}{3}\\right) &= 12 \\times \\left(14 + \\dfrac{6-x}{4}\\right)\\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{x}{2} + 12 \\times \\dfrac{x+1}{3} &= 12 \\times 14 + 12 \\times \\dfrac{6-x}{4}\\\\\n6x + 4(x+1) &= 168 + 3(6-x) \\\\\n6x + 4x + 4 &= 168 + 18 - 3x \\\\\n6x + 4x + 3x &= 168 + 18 - 4\\\\\n13x &= 182\\\\\n\\dfrac{13x}{13} &= \\dfrac{182}{13}\\\\\nx&=14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{x}{2} + \\dfrac{x+1}{3}  \\) if \\( x=14 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{14}{2} + \\dfrac{14+1}{3} \\\\\n&=7 + \\dfrac{15}{3} \\\\\n&=7+5\\\\\n&=12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  14 + \\dfrac{6-x}{4}\\) if \\( x=14 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=14+\\dfrac{6-14}{4}\\\\\n&=14 + \\dfrac{-8}{4}\\\\\n&=14 + -2\\\\\n&=12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 26",
        " 14",
        " 12",
        " 2"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x}{3} = \\dfrac{5x-9}{4} - \\dfrac{x - 1}{2} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x}{3} &= \\dfrac{5x-9}{4} - \\dfrac{x-1}{2}\\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{5x-9}{4} - \\dfrac{x-1}{2}\\right)\\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{x}{3} &= 12 \\times \\dfrac{5x-9}{4} - 12 \\times \\dfrac{x-1}{2}\\\\\n4x &= 3(5x - 9) - 6(x-1)\\\\\n4x &= 15x - 27 -6x+6\\\\\n4x -15x+6x&=-27+6\\\\\n-5x&=-21\\\\\n\\dfrac{-5x}{-5} &= \\dfrac{-21}{-5}\\\\\nx&=4.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  \\dfrac{x}{3}\\) if \\( x= 4.2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{4.2}{3}\\\\\n&=1.4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{5x-9}{4} - \\dfrac{x-1}{2}  \\) if \\( x=4.2 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{5(4.2)-9}{4} - \\dfrac{4.2-1}{2}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{21-9}{4} - \\dfrac{3.2}{2}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{12}{4} - 1.6\\\\\n&=3-1.6\\\\\n&=1.4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 4.1",
        " 1.4",
        " 4.2",
        " 2.4"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5x-12}{3} - \\dfrac{3x-5}{7} = \\dfrac{x-6}{4} + \\dfrac{4}{21} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{5x-12}{3} - \\dfrac{3x-5}{7} &= \\dfrac{x-6}{4} + \\dfrac{4}{21}\\\\\n84 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{5x-12}{3} - \\dfrac{3x-5}{7} \\right) &= 84 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x-6}{4} + \\dfrac{4}{21}\\right)\\\\\n84 \\times \\dfrac{5x-12}{3} - 84 \\times \\dfrac{3x-5}{7}  &= 84 \\times \\dfrac{x-6}{4} + 84 \\times \\dfrac{4}{21}\\\\\n28(5x-12)-12(3x-5) &= 21(x-6) + 4 \\times 4\\\\\n140x - 336 - 36x + 60 &= 21x - 126 + 16\\\\\n140x - 36x - 21x &= -126 + 16 - 60 + 336\\\\\n83x &= 166\\\\\n\\dfrac{83x}{83} &= \\dfrac{166}{83}\\\\\nx&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  \\dfrac{5x-12}{3} - \\dfrac{3x-5}{7}\\) if \\( x= 2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{5(2)-12}{3} - \\dfrac{3(2)-5}{7}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{10-12}{3} - \\dfrac{6-5}{7}\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{2}{3} - \\dfrac{1}{7}\\\\\n&= -\\dfrac{17}{21}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  \\dfrac{x-6}{4} + \\dfrac{4}{21}\\) if \\( x= 2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{2-6}{4} + \\dfrac{4}{21}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-4}{4} + \\dfrac{4}{21}\\\\\n&= -1 + \\dfrac{4}{21}\\\\\n&= -\\dfrac{17}{21}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 2",
        " \\(-\\dfrac{17}{21}\\)",
        " 0.8",
        " 10"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{10x+4}{3} = \\dfrac{8x-7}{3} - \\dfrac{3x}{4} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{10x+4}{3} &=\\dfrac{8x-7}{3} - \\dfrac{3x}{4}\\\\\n12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{10x+4}{3}\\right) &= 12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{8x-7}{3} - \\dfrac{3x}{4}\\right) \\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{x}{4} - 12 \\times \\dfrac{10x+4}{3} &= 12 \\times \\dfrac{8x-7}{3} - 12 \\times \\dfrac{3x}{4} \\\\\n3x - 4(10x+4) &= 4(8x-7) - 9x\\\\\n3x - 40x - 16 &= 32x - 28 - 9x\\\\\n3x - 40x -32x + 9x &= -28 + 16\\\\\n-60x &= -12\\\\\n\\dfrac{-60x}{-60} &= \\dfrac{-12}{-60}\\\\\nx&=\\dfrac{1}{5}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{x}{4} - \\dfrac{10x+4}{3}  \\quad\\) if \\( x= \\dfrac{1}{5}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{0.2}{4} - \\dfrac{10(0.2)+4}{3}\\\\\n&=0.05 - \\dfrac{2+4}{3}\\\\\n&= 0.05 -\\dfrac{6}{3}\\\\\n&=0.05 - 2\\\\\n&=-1.95\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{8x-7}{3} - \\dfrac{3x}{4}  \\quad\\) if \\( x=\\dfrac{1}{5} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{8(0.2)-7}{3} - \\dfrac{3(0.2)}{4}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1.6-7}{3} - 0.15\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-5.4}{3} - 0.15\\\\\n&=-1.8-0.15\\\\\n&=-1.95\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -1.95",
        " \\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\)",
        " 5",
        " -2"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x-6}{11} - \\dfrac{3x-2}{7} + \\dfrac{125}{77} = 2x - 15 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x-6}{11} - \\dfrac{3x-2}{7} + \\dfrac{125}{77} &= 2x - 15\\\\\n77 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x-6}{11} - \\dfrac{3x-2}{7} + \\dfrac{125}{77}\\right) &= 77 \\times (2x - 15) \\\\\n77 \\times \\dfrac{x-6}{11} - 77 \\times \\dfrac{3x-2}{7} + 77 \\times \\dfrac{125}{77} &= 77 \\times 2x - 77 \\times 15 \\\\\n7(x-6) - 11(3x-2) + 125 &= 154x - 1155\\\\\n7x-42-33x+22+125 &= 154x-1155\\\\\n7x-33x-154x &= -1155-125-22+42\\\\\n-180x&=-1260\\\\\n\\dfrac{-180x}{-180}&=\\dfrac{-1260}{-180}\\\\\nx&=7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(  \\dfrac{x-6}{11} - \\dfrac{3x-2}{7} + \\dfrac{125}{77}\\) if \\( x=7 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{7-6}{11} - \\dfrac{3(7)-2}{7} + \\dfrac{125}{77}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{11} - \\dfrac{21-2}{7} + \\dfrac{125}{77}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{11} - \\dfrac{19}{7} + \\dfrac{125}{77}\\\\\n&=-1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2x - 15 \\) if \\( x=7 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(7)-15\\\\\n&=14-15\\\\\n&=-1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -6",
        " -1",
        " 15",
        " 7"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x+5}{2} - \\dfrac{9-x}{5} = \\dfrac{3x+2}{20} + \\dfrac{14}{5} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x+5}{2} - \\dfrac{9-x}{5} &= \\dfrac{3x+2}{20} + \\dfrac{14}{5}\\\\\n20 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x+5}{2} - \\dfrac{9-x}{5} \\right) &= 20 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{3x+2}{20} + \\dfrac{14}{5}\\right)\\\\\n20 \\times \\dfrac{x+5}{2} - 20 \\times \\dfrac{9-x}{5}  &= 20 \\times \\dfrac{3x+2}{20} + 20 \\times  \\dfrac{14}{5}\\\\\n10(x+5) - 4(9-x) &= 3x + 2 + 56 \\\\\n10x + 50 - 36 + 4x &= 3x + 58 \\\\\n10x + 4x - 3x &= 58 - 50 + 36 \\\\\n11x &= 44\\\\\n\\dfrac{11x}{11} &= \\dfrac{44}{11}\\\\\nx&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x+5}{2} - \\dfrac{9-x}{5}  \\) if \\( x=4 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{4+5}{2} - \\dfrac{9-4}{5}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9}{2} - \\dfrac{5}{5}\\\\\n&= \\dfrac{9}{2} - 1\\\\\n&= \\dfrac{7}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{3x+2}{20} + \\dfrac{14}{5} \\) if \\( x=4 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{3(4)+2}{20} + \\dfrac{14}{5}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{12+2}{20} + \\dfrac{14}{5}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{7}{10} + \\dfrac{14}{5}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{7}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 4",
        " 8",
        " -4",
        " 16"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(x-\\dfrac{x-4}{3}=7 \\dfrac{3}{4}-\\dfrac{x+8}{5}+\\dfrac{x-2}{4} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx-\\dfrac{x-4}{3}&=7 \\dfrac{3}{4}-\\dfrac{x+8}{5}+\\dfrac{x-2}{4} \\\\\nx-\\dfrac{x-4}{3}&=\\dfrac{31}{4}-\\dfrac{x+8}{5}+\\dfrac{x-2}{4} \\\\\n60 \\times \\left(x-\\dfrac{x-4}{3}\\right)&=60 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{31}{4}-\\dfrac{x+8}{5}+\\dfrac{x-2}{4}\\right) \\\\\n60 \\times x-60 \\times \\frac{x-4}{3}&=60 \\times \\frac{31}{4}-60 \\times \\frac{x+8}{5}+60 \\times \\frac{x-2}{4} \\\\\n60 x-20(x-4)&=465-12(x+8)+15(x-2)\\\\\n60 x-20 x+80&=465-12 x-96+15 x-30 \\\\\n60 x-20 x+12 x-15 x&=465-96-30-80 \\\\\n37x&=259\\\\\n\\dfrac{37 x}{37}&=\\dfrac{259}{37} \\\\\nx&=7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( x-\\dfrac{x-4}{3} \\) if \\( x=7 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=7-\\dfrac{7-4}{3}\\\\\n&=7-\\dfrac{3}{3}\\\\\n&=7-1\\\\\n&=6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 7 \\dfrac{3}{4}-\\dfrac{x+8}{5}+\\dfrac{x-2}{4} \\) if \\( x=7 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\frac{31}{4}-\\frac{7+8}{5}+\\frac{7-2}{4} \\\\\n&=\\frac{31}{4}-\\frac{15}{5}+\\frac{5}{4} \\\\\n&=\\frac{31}{4}-3+\\frac{5}{4} \\\\\n&=6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 6",
        " 7",
        " 13",
        " 1"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9 x-2}{2}-\\left(x-\\dfrac{x+4}{7}\\right) =36\\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{9 x-2}{2}-\\left(x-\\dfrac{x+4}{7}\\right) &=36\\\\\n14 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{9 x-2}{2}-\\left(x-\\dfrac{x+4}{7}\\right)\\right) &=14 \\times 36\\\\\n14 \\times \\dfrac{9 x-2}{2}-14 \\times\\left(x-\\dfrac{x+4}{7}\\right)&=504 \\\\\n7(9 x-2)-14 x+14 \\times\\dfrac{x+4}{7}&=504 \\\\\n63 x-14-14 x+2(x+4)&=504 \\\\\n63 x-14-14 x+2 x+8&=504 \\\\\n63 x-14 x+2 x&=504+14-8 \\\\\n51x&=510\\\\\n\\dfrac{51 x}{51}&=\\dfrac{510}{51} \\\\\nx&=10\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 36 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{9 x-2}{2}-\\left(x-\\dfrac{x+4}{7}\\right) \\) if \\( x=10 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{9(10)-2}{2}-\\left(10-\\dfrac{10+4}{7}\\right) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{90-2}{2}-\\left(10-\\dfrac{14}{7}\\right) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{88}{2}-(10-2) \\\\\n&=44-8 \\\\\n&=36\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 36",
        " 504",
        " 10",
        " 7"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3 x}{14}-\\dfrac{2 x-7}{21}+3 \\dfrac{1}{4}=\\dfrac{x-4}{4} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3 x}{14}-\\dfrac{2 x-7}{21}+3 \\dfrac{1}{4}&=\\dfrac{x-4}{4} \\\\\n\\dfrac{3 x}{14}-\\dfrac{2 x-7}{21}+\\dfrac{13}{4}&=\\dfrac{x-4}{4} \\\\\n84 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{3 x}{14}-\\dfrac{2 x-7}{21}+\\dfrac{13}{4}\\right)&=84 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x-4}{4}\\right) \\\\\n84 \\times \\dfrac{3 x}{14}-84 \\times \\dfrac{2 x-7}{21}+84 \\times \\dfrac{13}{4}&=84 \\times \\dfrac{x-4}{4} \\\\\n6(3 x)-4(2 x-7)+21(13)&=21(x-4) \\\\\n18 x-8 x+28+273&=21 x-84 \\\\\n18 x-8 x-21 x&=-84-273-28 \\\\\n-11x&=-385\\\\\n\\dfrac{-11 x}{-11}&=\\dfrac{-385}{-11} \\\\\n&x=35\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{3 x}{14}-\\dfrac{2 x-7}{21}+3 \\dfrac{1}{4} \\) if \\( x=35 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{3(35)}{14}  -\\dfrac{2(35)-7}{21}+\\dfrac{13}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{105}{14}  -\\dfrac{70-7}{21}+\\dfrac{13}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{15}{2}  -\\dfrac{63}{21}+\\dfrac{13}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{15}{2}  -3+\\dfrac{13}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{31}{4}\\\\\n&=7.75\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x-4}{4} \\) if \\( x=35 \\)</div>\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{35-4}{4}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{31}{4}\\\\\n&=7.75\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 35",
        " -35",
        " 11",
        " 53"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{18 x+1}{29}-\\dfrac{402-27 x}{12}=9-\\dfrac{471-54 x}{2} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{18 x+1}{29}-\\dfrac{402-27 x}{12}&=9-\\dfrac{471-54 x}{2} \\\\\n348 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{18 x+1}{29}-\\dfrac{402-27 x}{12}\\right)&=348 \\times \\left(9-\\dfrac{471-54 x}{2}\\right) \\\\\n348 \\times \\dfrac{18 x+1}{29}-348 \\times \\dfrac{402-27 x}{12}&=348 \\times 9-348 \\times \\dfrac{471-54x}{2} \\\\\n12(18 x+1)-29(402-27 x)&=3132-174(471-54 x) \\\\\n216 x+12-11658+783 x&=3132-81954+7396 x \\\\\n216 x+783 x-9396 x&=3132-81954+11658-12 \\\\\n-8397x &= -67176\\\\\n\\dfrac{-8397 x}{-8397}&=\\dfrac{-67176}{-8397} \\\\\nx&=8 \\\\\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{18 x+1}{29}-\\dfrac{402-27 x}{12} \\quad \\) if \\( x=8 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{18(8)+1}{29}-\\dfrac{402-27(8)}{12} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{144+1}{29}-\\dfrac{402-216}{12} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{145}{29}-\\dfrac{186}{12} \\\\\n&=5 - \\frac{31}{2} \\\\\n&= -\\frac{21}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 9-\\dfrac{471-54 x}{2} \\) if \\( x=8 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=9 -\\frac{471-54(8)}{2} \\\\\n&=9 -\\frac{471-432}{2} \\\\\n&=9 - \\frac{39}{2} \\\\\n&=-\\frac{21}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 8",
        " 16",
        " 348",
        " 12"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2 x}{3} =8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2 x}{3} &=8 \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{2 x}{3} &=3 \\times 8 \\\\\n2x &= 24 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2 x}{2} &=\\dfrac{24}{2} \\\\\nx &=12 \n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 8 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{2 x}{3} \\) if \\( x=12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{2(12)}{3}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{24}{3}\\\\\n&=8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -8",
        " 6",
        " 20",
        " 8"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5} y+\\dfrac{2}{5} y=1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{5} y+\\dfrac{2}{5} y&=1 \\\\\n5 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{3 y}{5}+ \\dfrac{2}{5} y\\right)&=5 \\times 1 \\\\\n5 \\times \\dfrac{3 y}{5}+5 \\times \\dfrac{2}{5} y&=5 \\\\\n3 y+2 y&=5 \\\\\n5y&=5\\\\\n\\dfrac{5 y}{5}&=\\dfrac{5}{5} \\\\\n&y=1\n \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 1 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{3}{5} y+\\dfrac{2 }{5}y \\) if \\( y=1 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{3}{5}(1)+\\dfrac{2}{5}(1) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{3}{5}+\\dfrac{2}{5} \\\\\n&=1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 1",
        " 2",
        " 5",
        " 7"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2 v}{3}=\\dfrac{5}{6}-\\dfrac{2 v}{3} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2 v}{3}&=\\dfrac{5}{6}-\\dfrac{2 v}{3} \\\\\n6 \\times \\dfrac{2 v}{3}&=6 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{5}{6}-\\dfrac{2 v}{3}\\right) \\\\\n6 \\times \\frac{2 v}{3}&=6\\times\\dfrac{5}{6}-6 \\times \\dfrac{2 v}{3} \\\\\n2(2 v)&=5-2(2 v) \\\\\n4 v&=5-4 v \\\\\n4 v+4 v&=5 \\\\\n8v&=5\\\\\n\\dfrac{8 v}{8}&=\\dfrac{5}{8} \\\\\nv&=0.625\n \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{2 v}{3} \\) if \\( v=0.625 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{2(0.625)}{3}\\\\\n&=0.41\\overline{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{5}{6}-\\dfrac{2 v}{3} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{5}{6}-\\dfrac{2(0.625)}{3} \\\\\n&=0.41\\overline{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -0.416",
        " 0.625",
        " -0.625",
        " 6.25"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{n}{8}+2 n-\\dfrac{5 n}{6}=\\dfrac{3 n}{4}+13 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{n}{8}+2 n-\\dfrac{5 n}{6}&=\\dfrac{3 n}{4}+13 \\\\\n24 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{n}{8}+2 n-\\dfrac{5 n}{6}\\right)&=24 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{3 n}{4}+13\\right) \\\\\n24 \\times \\dfrac{n}{8}+24 \\times 2 n-24 \\times \\dfrac{5 n}{6}&=24 \\times \\dfrac{3 n}{4}+24 \\times 13 \\\\\n3 n+48 n-20 n&=18 n+312 \\\\\n3 n+48 n-20 n-18 n&=312 \\\\\n13n&=312\\\\\n\\dfrac{13 n}{13}&=\\dfrac{312}{13} \\\\\nn&=24\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{n}{8}+2 n-\\dfrac{5 n}{6}\\)  if \\(n=24\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{24}{8}+2(24)-\\dfrac{5(24)}{6} \\\\\n&=3+48-\\dfrac{5(24)}{6} \\\\\n&=51-\\dfrac{120}{6} \\\\\n&=51-20 \\\\\n&=31\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{3 n}{4}+13 \\) if \\( n=24 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{3(24)}{4}  +13 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{72}{4}+13\\\\\n&=18+13\\\\\n&= 31\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 24",
        " 31",
        " 55",
        " 24"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 r+\\dfrac{3 r}{7}=\\dfrac{3 r+2}{4}+23 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2 r+\\dfrac{3 r}{7}&=\\dfrac{3 r+2}{4}+23 \\\\\n28 \\times \\left(2 r+\\dfrac{3 r}{7}\\right)&=28 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{3 r+2}{4}+23\\right) \\\\\n28 \\times 2 r+28 \\times \\dfrac{3 r}{7}&=28 \\times \\dfrac{3 r+2}{4}+28 \\times 23 \\\\\n56 r+12 r&=7(3 r+2)+644 \\\\\n56 r+12 r&=21 r+14+644 \\\\\n56 r+12 r-21 r&=14+644 \\\\\n47r&=658\\\\\n\\dfrac{47 r}{47}&=\\dfrac{658}{47} \\\\\nr&=14 \\\\\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate 2 r+\\(\\dfrac{3 r}{7}\\)  if \\(r=14\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(14)+\\dfrac{3(14)}{7} \\\\\n&=28+6 \\\\\n&=34\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{ 3 r+2}{4}+23 \\)  if \\(r=14\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{3(14)+2}{4} +23 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{42+2}{4} +23 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{44}{4} +23 \\\\\n&=11+23\\\\\n&=34\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 48",
        " 14",
        " 34",
        " 20"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7 x}{12}-\\dfrac{1}{4}=2 x-\\dfrac{5}{3} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{7 x}{12}-\\dfrac{1}{4}&=2 x-\\dfrac{5}{3} \\\\\n12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{7 x}{12}-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)&=12 \\times \\left(2 x-\\dfrac{5}{3}\\right) \\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{7 x}{12}-12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{4}&=12 \\times 2 x-12 \\times \\dfrac{5}{3} \\\\\n7 x-3&=24 x-20 \\\\\n-3+20&=24 x-7 x \\\\\n17&=17x\\\\\n\\dfrac{17}{17}&=\\dfrac{17 x}{17} \\\\\n1&=x\\\\\nx&=1 \\\\\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{7 x}{12}-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\) if  \\(x=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{7(1)}{12}-\\dfrac{1}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{3}\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2 x-\\dfrac{5}{3} \\) if  \\(x=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(1) -\\dfrac{5}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 1",
        " \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
        " 3",
        " -1"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{r-8}{2} =6-\\dfrac{r}{3} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{r-8}{2} &=6-\\dfrac{r}{3} \\\\\n6 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{r-8}{2}\\right) &=6 \\times \\left(6-\\dfrac{r}{3}\\right) \\\\\n6 \\times \\dfrac{r-8}{2} &=6 \\times 6-6 \\times \\dfrac{r}{3} \\\\\n3(r-8) &=36-2 r \\\\\n3 r-24 &=36-2 r \\\\\n3 r+2 r &=36+24 \\\\\n5r&=60\\\\\n\\dfrac{5 r}{5} &=\\dfrac{60}{5} \\\\\nr &=12 \\\\\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{r-8}{2} \\) if \\( r=12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{12-8}{2}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{4}{2}\\\\\n&=2\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 6-\\dfrac{r}{3} \\) if \\( r=12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=6  -\\dfrac{12}{3} \\\\\n&=6  - 4 \\\\\n&=2\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 4",
        " 14",
        " -14",
        " 12"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2 y+3}{5}-\\dfrac{y-3}{3}=2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2 y+3}{5}-\\dfrac{y-3}{3}&=2 \\\\\n15 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{2 y+3}{5}-\\dfrac{y-3}{3}\\right)&=15 \\times2 \\\\\n15 \\times \\dfrac{2 y+3}{5}-15 \\times \\dfrac{y-3}{3}&=30 \\\\\n3(2 y+3)-5(y-3)&=30 \\\\\n6 y+9-5 y+15&=30 \\\\\n6 y-5 y&=30-15-9 \\\\\ny&=6 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 2 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{2 y+3}{5}-\\dfrac{y-3}{3} \\) if \\( y=6 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{2(6)+3}{5}  -\\dfrac{6-3}{3} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{12+3}{5}  -\\dfrac{3}{3} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{15}{5}  - 1 \\\\\n&=3  - 1 \\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 2",
        " 8",
        " 6",
        " 4"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{y-1}{2}-\\dfrac{y-2}{3}=\\dfrac{2}{3}-\\dfrac{y-3}{4} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{y-1}{2}-\\dfrac{y-2}{3}&=\\dfrac{2}{3}-\\dfrac{y-3}{4} \\\\\n12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{y-1}{2}-\\dfrac{y-2}{3}\\right)&=12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{2}{3}-\\dfrac{y-3}{4}\\right) \\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{y-1}{2}-12 \\times \\dfrac{y-2}{3}&=12 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}-12 \\times \\dfrac{y-3}{4} \\\\\n6(y-1)-4(y-2)&=8-3(y-3) \\\\\n6 y-6-4 y+8&=8-3 y+9 \\\\\n6 y-4 y+3 y&=8+9-8+6 \\\\\n5 y&=15 \\\\\n\\dfrac{5 y}{5}&=\\dfrac{15}{5} \\\\\ny&=3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{y-1}{2}-\\dfrac{y-2}{3} \\) if \\( y=3 \\)</div>\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{3-1}{2}-\\dfrac{3-2}{3} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{2}{2} - \\dfrac{1}{3}\\\\\n&=1 - \\dfrac{1}{3}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{2}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{2}{3}-\\dfrac{3-y}{4} \\) if \\( y=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{2}{3}  -\\dfrac{3-3}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{2}{3} - \\dfrac{0}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{2}{3} - 0 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{2}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 3",
        " \\(\\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
        " -3",
        " \\(\\dfrac{5}{3}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{t-3}{7}+\\dfrac{t+5}{3}-\\dfrac{t+2}{6}=4 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{t-3}{7}+\\dfrac{t+5}{3}-\\dfrac{t+2}{6}&=4 \\\\\n42 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{t-3}{7}+\\dfrac{t+5}{3}-\\dfrac{t+2}{6}\\right)&=42 \\times 4\\\\\n42 \\times \\dfrac{t-3}{7}+42 \\times \\dfrac{t+5}{3}-42 \\times \\dfrac{t+2}{6}&=168\\\\\n6(t-3)+14(t+5)-7(t+2)&=168 \\\\\n6 t-18+14 t+70-7 t-14&=168 \\\\\n6 t+14 t-7 t&=168+14-70+18 \\\\\n13t &= 130 \\\\\n\\dfrac{13 t}{13}&=\\dfrac{130}{13} \\\\\nt&=10 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 4 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{t-3}{7}+\\dfrac{t+5}{3}-\\dfrac{t+2}{6} \\) if \\( t=10 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{10-3}{7}+\\dfrac{10+5}{3}-\\dfrac{10+2}{6} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{7}{7}+\\dfrac{15}{3}-\\dfrac{12}{6} \\\\\n&=1+5-2\\\\\n&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 4",
        " 14",
        " 6",
        " 10"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{4}(6-x)=5 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{5}{4}(6-x)&=5 \\\\\n4 \\times \\dfrac{5}{4}(6-x)&=4 \\times 5 \\\\\n5(6-x)&=20 \\\\\n30-5 x&=20 \\\\\n-5 x&=20-30 \\\\\n-5x&=-10\\\\\n\\dfrac{-5 x}{-5}&=\\dfrac{-10}{-5} \\\\\nx&=2 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 5 </div>\n\n <div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{5}{4}(6-x)\\) if \\( x=2 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n &=\\dfrac{5}{4}(6-2) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{5}{4}({4})\\\\\n&=5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 5",
        " 2",
        " 7",
        " 3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4 s+2}{11}=\\dfrac{1}{5}(s+5) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{4 s+2}{11}&=\\dfrac{1}{5}(s+5) \\\\\n55 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{4 s+2}{11}\\right)&=55\\times\\left(\\dfrac{1}{5}(s+5)\\right) \\\\\n55 \\times \\dfrac{4s+2}{11}&=55 \\times \\dfrac{1}{5}(s+5) \\\\\n5(4s+2)&=11(s+5) \\\\\n20 s+10&=11s+55 \\\\\n20s-11s&=55-10 \\\\\n9s&=45\\\\\n\\dfrac{9s}{9}&=\\dfrac{45}{9} \\\\\ns&=5 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n <div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{4 s+2}{11} \\) if \\( s=5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{4(5)+2}{11} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{20+2}{11}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{22}{11}\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{1}{5}(s+5) \\) if \\( s=5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1}{5}(5+5) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{5}(10)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{10}{5}\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 2",
        " -5",
        " 5",
        " 7"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{5}(t+1)=2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{4}{5}(t+1)&=2 \\\\\n5 \\times \\dfrac{4}{5}(t+1)&=5 \\times 2 \\\\\n4(t+1)&=10 \\\\\n4 t+4&=10 \\\\\n4 t&=10-4 \\\\\n4t&=6\\\\\n\\dfrac{4 t}{4}&=\\dfrac{6}{4} \\\\\nt&=1.5 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 2 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{4}{5}(t+1)\\) if  \\(t=1.5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{4}{5}(1.5+1)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{4}{5}(2.5)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{10}{5}\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 2",
        " 1.5",
        " 3.5",
        " -1.5"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}(s+4)-\\dfrac{1}{6} s-8=0 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{2}(s+4)-\\dfrac{1}{6} s-8&=0 \\\\\n6 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}(s+4)-\\dfrac{1}{6} s-8\\right)&=6 \\times 0 \\\\\n6\\times \\dfrac{1}{2}(s+4)-6\\times\\dfrac{1}{6}s-6 \\times 8&=0 \\\\\n3(s+4)-s-48&=0 \\\\\n3s+12-s-48&=0 \\\\\n3s-s&=48-12 \\\\\n2s&=36\\\\\n\\dfrac{2s}{2}&=\\dfrac{36}{2} \\\\\ns&=18 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{1}{2}(s+4)-\\dfrac{1s}{6}-8 \\) if \\( s=18 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1}{2}(18+4)-\\dfrac{1(18)}{6}-8 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{22}{2}-\\dfrac{18}{6}-8\\\\\n&=11-3-8\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 0",
        " -18",
        " 18",
        " 36"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.5x = 3 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.5x&=3\\\\\n\\dfrac{0.5 x}{0.5}&=\\dfrac{3}{0.5} \\\\\nx&=6 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 3 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 0.5 x \\) if \\( x=6 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=0.5(6)\\\\\n&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 6",
        " 3",
        " 9",
        " -3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.2 x=48-0.04 x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.2 x&=48-0.04 x \\\\\n0.2 x+0.04 x&=48 \\\\\n0.24x&=48\\\\\n\\dfrac{0.24 x}{0.24}&=\\dfrac{48}{0.24} \\\\\nx&=200\n \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 0.2 x \\) if \\( x=200 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=0.2(200) \\\\\n&=40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 48-0.04 x \\) if \\( x=200 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=48-0.04(200) \\\\\n&=48-8 \\\\\n&=40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 40",
        " 240",
        " 200",
        " -200"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.2 w+3 =3.8+0.04 w \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.2 w+3 &=3.8+0.04 w \\\\\n0.2 w-0.04 w &=3.8-3 \\\\\n0.16w&=0.8\\\\\n\\dfrac{0.16 w}{0.16} &=\\dfrac{0.8}{0.16} \\\\\nw &=5 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 0.2 w+3 \\) if \\( w=5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=0.2(5)+3 \\\\\n&=1+3\\\\\n&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3.8+0.04 w \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3.8+0.04(5) \\\\\n&=3.8+0.2\\\\\n&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 4",
        " 9",
        " 1",
        " 5"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{8}(z+2)+\\dfrac{2}{3}(z-12)=\\dfrac{1}{5}(z+9) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{7}{8}(z+2)+\\dfrac{2}{3}(z-12)&=\\dfrac{1}{5}(z+9) \\\\\n120 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{7}{8}(z+2)+\\dfrac{2}{3}(z-12)\\right)&=120 \\times \\dfrac{1}{5}(z+9) \\\\\n120 \\times \\dfrac{7}{8}(z+2)+120 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}(z-12)&=24(z+9) \\\\\n105(z+2)+80(z-12)&=24(z+9) \\\\\n105 z +210+80 z-960&=24 z+216 \\\\\n105 z+80 z-24 z&=216+960-210 \\\\\n161z&=966\\\\\n\\dfrac{161 z}{161}&=\\dfrac{966}{161} \\\\\nz&=6 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{7}{8}(z+2)+\\dfrac{2}{3}(z-12) \\) if \\( z=6 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{7}{8}(6+2)+\\dfrac{2}{3}(6-12) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{7}{8}(8)+\\dfrac{2}{3}(-6) \\\\\n&=7+\\dfrac{-12}{3} \\\\\n&=7-4\\\\\n&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{1}{5}(z+9) \\) if \\( z=6 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1}{5}(6+9)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{15}{5}\\\\\n&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -6",
        " 6",
        " 360",
        " 105"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 y-5=\\dfrac{2 y+10}{6} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2 y-5&=\\dfrac{2 y+10}{6} \\\\\n6 \\times (2 y-5)&=6\\times  \\dfrac{2 y+10}{6} \\\\\n6 \\times 2 y-6 \\times 5&=2 y+10\\\\\n12 y-30&=2 y+10 \\\\\n12 y-2 y&=10+30 \\\\\n10y&=40\\\\\n\\dfrac{10 y}{10}&=\\dfrac{40}{10} \\\\\ny&=4 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2y-5\\) if \\( y=4 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(4)-5 \\\\\n&=8-5 \\\\\n&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{2 y+10}{6} \\) if \\( y=4 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{2(4)+10}{6} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{8+10}{6}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{18}{6}\\\\\n&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 3",
        " -3",
        " 4",
        " 7"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x+2}{4} =\\dfrac{x+12}{9} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x+2}{4} &=\\dfrac{x+12}{9} \\\\\n36 \\times \\dfrac{x+2}{4} &=36 \\times \\dfrac{x+12}{9} \\\\\n9(x+2) &=4(x+12) \\\\\n9 x+18 &=4 x+48 \\\\\n9 x-4 x &=48-18 \\\\\n5x&=30\\\\\n\\dfrac{5 x}{5} &=\\dfrac{30}{5} \\\\\nx &=6 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x+2}{4} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{6+2}{4}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{8}{4}\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x+12}{9} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{6+12}{9} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{18}{9}\\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 6",
        " 9",
        " 2",
        " 8"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x-2}{5}+\\dfrac{x}{3}=\\dfrac{x}{2} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x-2}{5}+\\dfrac{x}{3}&=\\dfrac{x}{2} \\\\\n30 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x-2}{5}+\\dfrac{x}{3}\\right)&=30 \\times \\dfrac{x}{2} \\\\\n30 \\times \\dfrac{x-2}{5}+30 \\times \\dfrac{x}{3}&=15x \\\\\n6(x-2)+10 x&=15 x \\\\\n6 x-12+10 x&=15 x \\\\\n-12&=15 x-10 x-6 x \\\\\n-12&=-x \\\\\n-x&=-12\\\\\nx&=12 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x-2}{5}+\\dfrac{x}{3} \\) if \\( x=12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{12-2}{5}+\\dfrac{12}{3} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{10}{5}+4 \\\\\n&=2+4\\\\\n&=6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x}{2} \\) if \\( x =12 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{12}{2} \\\\\n&=6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 12",
        " -12",
        " 6",
        " \\(\\dfrac{12}{6}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x-4}{3} =\\dfrac{x-11}{10} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x-4}{3} &=\\dfrac{x-11}{10} \\\\\n30 \\times \\dfrac{x-4}{3} &=30 \\times \\dfrac{x-11}{10} \\\\\n10(x-4) &=3(x-11) \\\\\n10 x-40 &=3 x-33 \\\\\n10 x-3 x &=-33+40 \\\\\n7x&=7\\\\\n\\dfrac{7 x}{7} &=\\dfrac{7}{7} \\\\\nx &=1 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x-4}{3}\\) if \\( x=1 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1-4}{3}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-3}{3}\\\\\n&=-1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x-11}{10} \\) if \\( x =1 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1-11}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-10}{10}\\\\\n&=-1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -1",
        " 2",
        " 1",
        " 0"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4 x+3}{3}-\\dfrac{6 x+7}{5}=0 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{4 x+3}{3}-\\dfrac{6 x+7}{5}&=0 \\\\\n15 \\times \\left( \\dfrac{4 x+3}{3}-\\dfrac{6 x+7}{5} \\right)&=0 \\\\\n15\\left(\\dfrac{4 x+3}{3}\\right)-15\\left(\\dfrac{6 x+7}{5}\\right)&=0 \\\\\n5(4 x+3)-3(6 x+7)&=0 \\\\\n20 x+15-18 x-21&=0 \\\\\n20 x-18 x&=21-15 \\\\\n2x&=6\\\\\n\\dfrac{2 x}{2}&=\\dfrac{6}{2} \\\\\nx&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{4 x+3}{3}-\\dfrac{6 x+7}{5} \\) if \\( x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{4 (3)+3}{3}-\\dfrac{6 (3)+7}{5}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{12+3}{3}-\\dfrac{18+7}{5} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{15}{3}-\\dfrac{25}{5} \\\\\n&=5-5\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -3",
        " 0",
        " 9",
        " 3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{x+6}{10}-\\dfrac{x+1}{4}=2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{x+6}{10}-\\dfrac{x+1}{4}&=2 \\\\\n40 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{x+6}{10}-\\dfrac{x+1}{4}\\right)&=40 \\times 2 \\\\\n40 \\times \\dfrac{x+6}{10}-40 \\times \\dfrac{x+1}{4}&=80 \\\\\n4(x+6)-10(x+1)&=80 \\\\\n4 x+24-10 x-10&=80 \\\\\n4 x-10 x&=80-24+10 \\\\\n-6x&=66\\\\\n\\dfrac{-6 x}{-6}&=\\dfrac{66}{-6} \\\\\nx&=-11\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 2 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{x+6}{10}-\\dfrac{x+1}{4} \\) if \\( x=-11 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{-11+6}{10} -\\dfrac{-11+1}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-5}{10} -\\dfrac{-10}{4} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{1}{2} +\\dfrac{5}{2} \\\\\n&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -11",
        " 2",
        " 11",
        " 9"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3 x+6}{5}=2 x-3 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3 x+6}{5}&=2 x-3 \\\\\n5 \\times \\dfrac{3 x+6}{5}&=5 \\times (2 x-3) \\\\\n3 x+6&=5(2x-3) \\\\\n3 x+6&=10 x-15 \\\\\n3 x-10 x&=-15-6 \\\\\n-7x&=-21\\\\\n\\dfrac{-7 x}{-7}&=\\dfrac{-21}{-7} \\\\\nx&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{3 x+6}{5} \\) if \\( x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{3(3)+6}{5}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9+6}{5}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{15}{5}\\\\\n&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2x-3\\) if \\( x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(3)-3\\\\\n&=6-3\\\\\n&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -3",
        " 6",
        " 3",
        " 10"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2 y+6}{3}=3 y-5 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2 y+6}{3}&=3 y-5 \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{2 y+6}{3}&=3 \\times (3 y-5 ) \\\\\n2 y+6&=3(3 y-5) \\\\\n2 y+6&=9 y-15 \\\\\n2 y-9 y&=-15-6 \\\\\n-7y&=-21\\\\\n\\dfrac{-7 y}{-7}&=\\dfrac{-21}{-7} \\\\\ny&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{2 y+6}{3} \\) if \\( y=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{2(3)+6}{3}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{6+6}{3}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{12}{3}\\\\\n&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3y-5\\) if \\( y=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(3)-5\\\\\n&=9-5\\\\\n&=4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 4",
        " 3",
        " 7",
        " -3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{p}{4}-\\dfrac{3 p}{8}=\\dfrac{1}{6} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{p}{4}-\\dfrac{3 p}{8}&=\\dfrac{1}{6} \\\\ \n24 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{p}{4}-\\dfrac{3 p}{8}\\right)&=24 \\times \\dfrac{1}{6} \\\\ \n24 \\times \\dfrac{p}{4}-24 \\times \\dfrac{3 p}{8}&=4 \\\\ \n6 p-9 p&=4 \\\\ \n\\dfrac{-3 p}{-3}&=\\dfrac{4}{-3} \\\\ \np&=-\\dfrac{4}{3} \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = \\(\\dfrac{1}{6}\\) </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{p}{4}-\\dfrac{3 p}{8}\\) if \\(p=-\\dfrac{4}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{-\\dfrac{4}{3}}{4}-\\dfrac{3\\left(\\dfrac{-4}{3}\\right)}{8} \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{-4}{12}-\\dfrac{-4}{8} \\\\ \n&=-\\dfrac{1}{3}+\\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{1}{6} \n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " \\(\\dfrac{1}{6}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
        " \\(-\\dfrac{4}{3}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{4}{3}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{q}{2}-\\dfrac{5 q}{6}=\\dfrac{1}{9} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{q}{2}-\\dfrac{5 q}{6}&=\\dfrac{1}{9} \\\\\n54 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{q}{2}-\\dfrac{5 q}{6}\\right)&=54 \\times \\dfrac{1}{9} \\\\\n54 \\times \\dfrac{q}{2}-54 \\times \\dfrac{5 q}{6}&=6\\\\\n27 q-45 q&=6 \\\\\n-18q&=6\\\\\n\\dfrac{-18 q}{-18}&=\\dfrac{6}{-18} \\\\\nq&=-\\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = \\(\\dfrac{1}{9}\\) </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{q}{2}-\\dfrac{5 p}{6}\\) if \\(p=-\\dfrac{1}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{3}\\right)}{2}- \\dfrac{5\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{3}\\right)}{6}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1}{6}-\\dfrac{\\,\\dfrac{-5}{3}\\,}{6} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{1}{6}+\\dfrac{5}{18} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{9}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " \\(\\dfrac{1}{9}\\)",
        " \\(-\\dfrac{1}{9}\\)",
        " 3",
        " \\(-\\dfrac{1}{3}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{z}{4}-\\dfrac{3}{5}=\\dfrac{z}{3}+\\dfrac{2}{7} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{z}{4}-\\dfrac{3}{5}&=\\dfrac{z}{3}+\\dfrac{2}{7} \\\\\n420 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{z}{4}-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)&=420 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{z}{3}+\\dfrac{2}{7}\\right) \\\\\n420 \\times \\dfrac{z}{4}-420 \\times \\dfrac{3}{5}&=420 \\times \\dfrac{z}{3}+420 \\times \\dfrac{2}{7}\\\\\n105 z-252&=140 z+120 \\\\\n105 z-140 z&=120+252 \\\\\n-35z&=372\\\\\n\\dfrac{-35 z}{-35}&=\\dfrac{372}{-35} \\\\\nz&=-\\dfrac{372}{35}\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{z}{4}-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\) if  \\(z=-\\dfrac{372}{35}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{\\left(-\\dfrac{372}{35}\\right)}{4}-\\dfrac{3}{5} \\\\\n&= -\\dfrac{93}{35}-\\dfrac{3}{5} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{114}{35}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{z}{3}+\\dfrac{2}{7}\\) if  \\(z=-\\dfrac{372}{35}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{\\left(-\\dfrac{372}{35}\\right)}{3}+\\dfrac{2}{7} \\\\\n&= -\\dfrac{124}{35}+\\dfrac{2}{7} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{114}{35}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " \\(-\\dfrac{372}{35}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{372}{35}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{35}{372}\\)",
        " \\(-\\dfrac{35}{372}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{w}{5}-\\dfrac{2}{3}=\\dfrac{w}{6}-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{w}{5}-\\dfrac{2}{3}&=\\dfrac{w}{6}-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\\n30 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{w}{5}-\\dfrac{2}{3}\\right)&=30 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{w}{6}-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) \\\\\n30 \\times \\dfrac{w}{5}-30 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}&=30 \\times \\dfrac{w}{6}-30 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\\n6 w-20&=5 w-15 \\\\\n6 w-5 w&=-15+20 \\\\\nw&=5\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{w}{5}-\\dfrac{2}{3} \\) if \\( w=5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{5}{5}-\\dfrac{2}{3} \\\\\n&=1-\\dfrac{2}{3} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{w}{6}-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\) if \\( w=5 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{5}{6}-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 5",
        " \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
        " 10",
        " \\(\\dfrac{5}{3}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3}(2 x-4)=\\dfrac{1}{5}\\left(10+\\dfrac{x}{6}\\right) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}(2 x-4)&=\\dfrac{1}{5}\\left(10+\\dfrac{x}{6}\\right) \\\\\n15 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}(2 x-4)&=15 \\times \\dfrac{1}{5}\\left(10+\\dfrac{x}{6}\\right) \\\\\n5(2 x-4)&=3\\left(10+\\dfrac{x}{6}\\right) \\\\\n10 x-20&=30+\\dfrac{3 x}{6} \\\\\n6 \\times (10 x-20)&=6 \\times \\left(30+\\dfrac{3 x}{6}\\right) \\\\\n6 (10 x- 20)&=6 \\times 30+6 \\times \\dfrac{3 x}{6} \\\\\n60 x-120&=180+3 x \\\\\n60 x-3 x&=180+120 \\\\\n57x&=300\\\\\n\\dfrac{57 x}{57}&=\\dfrac{300}{57} \\\\\nx&=\\dfrac{300}{57}\\\\\nx&=\\dfrac{100}{19}\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{1}{3}(2 x-4)\\) if \\(x= \\dfrac{100}{19}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1}{3}\\left(2\\left(\\dfrac{100}{19}\\right)-4\\right) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{3}\\left(\\dfrac{124}{19}\\right) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{124}{57}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( \\dfrac{1}{5}\\left(10+\\dfrac{x}{6}\\right) \\) if \\(x= \\dfrac{100}{19} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\dfrac{1}{5}\\left(10+\\dfrac{\\,\\dfrac{100}{19}\\,}{6}\\right)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{5}\\left(10+\\dfrac{50}{57}\\right)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{5}\\left(\\dfrac{620}{57}\\right)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{124}{57}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " \\(-\\dfrac{100}{19}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{100}{19}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{19}{100}\\)",
        " \\(-\\dfrac{19}{100}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7\\left(\\dfrac{x}{2}+12\\right)-\\dfrac{1}{4}(3 x-1)=0 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7\\left(\\dfrac{x}{2}+12\\right)-\\dfrac{1}{4}(3 x-1)&=0 \\\\\n7\\left(\\dfrac{x}{2}+12\\right)-\\dfrac{1}{4}(3 x-1)&=0 \\\\\n\\dfrac{7 x}{2}+84-\\dfrac{1}{4}(3 x-1)&=0 \\\\\n8 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{7 x}{2}+84-\\dfrac{1}{4}(3 x-1)\\right) &= 8 \\times 0 \\\\\n8 \\times \\dfrac{7 x}{2}+8 \\times 84-8 \\times \\dfrac{1}{4}(3 x-1)&=0 \\\\\n28 x+672-2(3 x-1)&=0 \\\\\n28 x+672-6 x+2&=0 \\\\\n28 x-6 x&=-672-2 \\\\\n22x&=-674\\\\\n\\dfrac{22 x}{22}&=-\\dfrac{674}{22} \\\\\nx&=\\dfrac{-337}{11}\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 7\\left(\\dfrac{x}{2}+12\\right)-\\dfrac{1}{4}(3 x-1) \\) if \\(x=  -\\dfrac{337}{11} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=7\\left(\\dfrac{\\left(-\\dfrac{337}{11}\\right) }{2}+12\\right)-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\left(3 \\left(-\\dfrac{337}{11}\\right) -1\\right) \\\\\n&=7\\left(-\\dfrac{337}{22}+12\\right)-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\left(-\\dfrac{1011}{11} -1\\right)\\\\\n&=7\\left(-\\dfrac{73}{22}\\right)-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\left(-\\dfrac{1022}{11} \\right)\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{511}{22} + \\dfrac{511}{22}\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " \\(\\dfrac{-337}{11}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{337}{11}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{11}{337}\\)",
        " \\(\\dfrac{-11}{337}\\)"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(x-3)=2(x+1) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(x-3)&=2(x+1) \\\\\n4 x-12&=2 x+2 \\\\\n4 x-2 x&=2+12 \\\\\n2x&=14\\\\\n\\dfrac{2 x}{2}&=\\dfrac{14}{2} \\\\\nx&=7\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 4(x-3) \\) if \\( x=7 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(7-3) \\\\\n&=4(4)\\\\\n&=16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2(x+1) \\) if \\( x=7 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(7+1) \\\\\n&=2(8)\\\\\n&=16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 16",
        " 7",
        " 9",
        " 23"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(x-5)=3(x+1) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(x-5)&=3(x+1) \\\\\n4 x-20&=3 x+3 \\\\\n4 x-3 x&=3+20 \\\\\nx&=23\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 4(x-5) \\) if \\( x=23 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(23-5) \\\\\n&=4(18)\\\\\n&=72\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3(x+1) \\) if \\( x=23 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(23+1) \\\\\n&=3(24)\\\\\n&=72\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 23",
        " 20",
        " 72",
        " 49"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(x-2)=7(x-5) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(x-2)&=7(x-5) \\\\\n4 x-8&=7 x-35 \\\\\n4 x-7 x&=-35+8 \\\\\n-3x&=-27\\\\\n-\\dfrac{3 x}{-3}&=\\dfrac{-27}{-3} \\\\\nx&=9\n\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 4(x-2) \\) if \\( x=9 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(9-2) \\\\\n&=4(7)\\\\\n&=28\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 7(x-5) \\) if \\( x=9 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=7(9-5) \\\\\n&=7(4)\\\\\n&=28\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 28",
        " 19",
        " 10",
        " 9"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(2 y+1)=2(3 y+5) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(2 y+1)&=2(3 y+5) \\\\\n8 y+4&=6 y+10 \\\\\n8 y-6 y&=10-4 \\\\\n2y&=6\\\\\n\\dfrac{2 y}{2}&=\\dfrac{6}{2} \\\\\ny&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 4(2y+1) \\) if \\( y=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(2(3)+1) \\\\\n&=4(6+1)\\\\\n&=4(7)\\\\\n&=28\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2(3y+5) \\) if \\( y=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(3(3)+5) \\\\\n&=2(9+5)\\\\\n&=2(14)\\\\\n&=28\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 3",
        " 28",
        " -3",
        " 31"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(2 w-1)+5(3 w-4)=22 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(2 w-1)+5(3 w-4)&=22 \\\\\n8 w-4+15 w-20&=22 \\\\\n8 w+15 w&=22+20+4 \\\\\n23w&=46\\\\\n\\dfrac{23 w}{23}&=\\dfrac{46}{23} \\\\\nw&=2\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 22 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(2 w-1)+5(3 w-4)\\) if  \\(w=2\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(2(2)-1)+5(3(2)-4) \\\\\n&=4(4-1)+5(6-4)\\\\\n&=4(3)+5(2)\\\\\n&=12+10\\\\\n&=22\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 24",
        " 22",
        " 2",
        " -2"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(2 m+2)+5(3 m-5)=52 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(2 m+2)+5(3 m-5)&=52 \\\\\n8 m+8+15 m-25&=52 \\\\\n8 m+15 m&=52+25-8 \\\\\n23m&=69\\\\\n\\dfrac{23 m}{23}&=\\dfrac{69}{23} \\\\\nm&=3\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 52 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(2 m+2)+5(3 m-5)\\) if  \\(m=3\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(2(3)+2)+5(3(3)-5) \\\\\n&=4(6+2)+5(9-5) \\\\\n&=4(8)+5(4) \\\\\n&=32+20\\\\\n&=52\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 52",
        " 75",
        " 19",
        " 3"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3(3 n-5)+4(5 n+2)=3 n+149 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3(3 n-5)+4(5 n+2)&=3 n+149 \\\\\n9 n-15+20 n+8&=3 n+149 \\\\\n9 n+20 n-3 n&=149-8+15 \\\\\n26n&=156\\\\\n\\dfrac{26 n}{26}&=\\dfrac{156}{26} \\\\\nn&=6\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3(3 n-5)+4(5 n+2)\\) if  \\(n=6\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(3(6)-5)+4(5(6)+2) \\\\\n&=3(18-5)+4(30+2) \\\\\n&=3(13)+4(32) \\\\\n&=39+128 \\\\\n&=167\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\((3 n+149)\\) if  \\(n=6\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(6)+149\\\\\n&=18+149\\\\\n&=167\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 167",
        " 6",
        " 161",
        " 173"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7-3(2-3 p)=28 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7-3(2-3 p)&=28 \\\\\n7-6+9 p&=28 \\\\\n9 p&=28-7+6 \\\\\n9p&=27\\\\\n\\dfrac{9 p}{9}&=\\dfrac{27}{9}\\\\\np&=3\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 28 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7-3(2-3 p)\\) if  \\(p=3\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=7-3(2-3(3)) \\\\\n&=7-3(2-9)\\\\\n&=7-3(-7)\\\\\n&=7+21\\\\\n&=28\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 31",
        " 28",
        " 3",
        " 25"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(13-5(3-2 q)=48 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n13-5(3-2 q)&=48 \\\\\n13-15+10 q&=48 \\\\\n10 q&=48+15-13 \\\\\n10q&=50\\\\\n\\dfrac{10 q}{10}&=\\dfrac{50}{10} \\\\\nq&=5\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 48 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(13-5(3-2 q)\\) if  \\(q=5\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=13-5(3-2(5)) \\\\\n&=13-5(3-10)\\\\\n&=13-5(-7)\\\\\n&=13+35\\\\\n&=48\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 5",
        " 48",
        " 53",
        " 43"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(3 n-2)-3(5 n+2)=4 n-75 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(3 n-2)-3(5 n+2)&=4 n-75 \\\\\n6 n-4-15 n-6&=4 n-75 \\\\\n6 n-15 n-4 n&=-75+6+4 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-13 n}{-13}&=\\dfrac{-65}{-13} \\\\\nn&=5\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(3 n-2)-3(5 n+2)\\) if  \\(n=5\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(3(5)-2)  -3(5(5)+2) \\\\\n&=2(15-2)  -3(25+2) \\\\\n&=2(13)  -3(27) \\\\\n&=26  -81 \\\\\n&=-55\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4n-75\\) if  \\(n=5\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(5)-75 \\\\\n&=20-75\\\\\n&=-55\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " -55",
        " 5",
        " -5",
        " 60"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(5s-2)-5(2 s+7)=200 s-1563 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(5s-2)-5(2 s+7)&=200 s-1563 \\\\\n20 s-8-10 s-35&=200 s-1563 \\\\\n20 s-10 s-200 s&=-1563+35+8 \\\\\n-190s&=-1520\\\\\n\\dfrac{-190 s}{-190}&=\\dfrac{-1520}{-190} \\\\\ns&=8\n\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(5s-2)-5(2 s+7)\\) if  \\(s=8\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(5(8)-2) -5(2(8)+7) \\\\\n&=4(40-2)-5(16+7)\\\\\n&=4(38)-5(23)\\\\\n&=152-115\\\\\n&=37\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(200 s-1563\\) if  \\(s=8\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=200(8)-1563 \\\\\n&=1600-1563\\\\\n&=37\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 8",
        " 16",
        " 30",
        " 56"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(5 x+3)-6(2 x-1)=3(x+14) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(5 x+3)-6(2 x-1)&=3(x+14) \\\\\n10 x+6-12 x+6&=3 x+42 \\\\\n10 x-12 x-3 x&=42-6-6 \\\\\n-5x&=30\\\\\n\\dfrac{-5 x}{-5}&=\\dfrac{30}{-5} \\\\\nx&=-6\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(5 x+3)-6(2 x-1)\\) if  \\(x=-6\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(5(-6)+3)  -6(2(-6)-1) \\\\\n&=2(-30+3)-6(-12-1)\\\\\n&=2(-27)-6(-13)\\\\\n&=-54+78\\\\\n&=24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3(x+14)\\) if  \\(x=-6\\) </div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3(-6+14) \\\\\n&=3(8)\\\\\n&=24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]",
      "choices": [
        " 60",
        " 0",
        " 24",
        " -6"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 t+4=12+3 t \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3 t+4&=12+3 t \\\\\n3 t-3 t&=12-4 \\\\\n0&=8\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>\nSince \\(0=8\\) is always false, no value of \\(t\\) satisfies the equation\n</div>",
      "choices": [
        " 8",
        " 3",
        " 4",
        " No solution"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12 y+6=6(2 y+1) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n12 y+6&=6(2 y+1) \\\\\n12 y+6&=12 y+6 \\\\\n12 y-12 y&=6-6 \\\\\n0&=0\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>\nSince \\(0=0\\) is always true, any value of \\(y\\) satisfies the equation\n</div>",
      "choices": [
        " All numbers satisfy the equation",
        " 8 only",
        " 3 only",
        " 12 only"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3(4 g+6)=2(6 g+9) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3(4 g+6)&=2(6 g+9) \\\\\n12 g+18&=12 g+18 \\\\\n12 g-12 g&=18-18 \\\\\n0&=0\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>\nSince \\(0=0\\) is always true, any value of \\(g\\) satisfies the equation\n</div>",
      "choices": [
        " 20 only",
        " 8 only",
        " All numbers satisfy the equation",
        " 5only"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5(1+2 m)=\\dfrac{1}{2}(8+20 m) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5(1+2 m)&=\\dfrac{1}{2}(8+20 m) \\\\\n2 \\times 5(1+2 m)&=2 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2}(8+20 m) \\\\\n10(1+2 m)&=8+20 m \\\\\n10+20 m&=8+20 m \\\\\n20 m-20 m&=8-10 \\\\\n0&=-2\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>\nSince \\(0=-2\\) is always false, no value of \\(m\\) satisfies the equation\n</div>",
      "choices": [
        " -5",
        " 7",
        " No solution",
        " 1"
      ],
      "correctChoice": 2
    }
  ]
}
